tribalshapes.com 2014-04-29

# Privacy policy

Please read carefully this privacy policy before using the website or submitting any personal information. By using this website, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the website to be up to date with its content (though it may change as needed) and make sure you understand how any personal information you provide can be used.

Note, that the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you follow links to other web sites, please review the privacy policies stated at those sites.

## Collection of information

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, email addresses and/or interests, when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, that may be for example, using your e-mail address to respond a message you sent through our contact form.

## Cookies and tracking technologies

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, refer to the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be stated at this document.
